Ricky Vu

My name is Ricky Vu and I am a current student at Indiana University studying Informatics. I have a passion for technology and chose to further my knowledge on it by going to University. I have no prior experience with web design or programming but I have a true determination to keep on learning on what the field has to offer

9018 Crystal Lake Dr. Indianapolis, IN 46240 (317)-772-6976 rickyyvu15@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Panda Restaurant Group, Indiana — Associate

June 2021 - July 2022

Duties were to keep the restaurant clean, cash handling, serve customers and make food from time to time.

TJX, Indiana — Associate

November 2020- May 2021

Stock items and be on call for backup cashiering. Also greet customers from time to time

Smoothie King Enterprise, Indiana — Shift Supervisor

July 2020- November 2020

Create smoothies and direct the team to reach sales goals during shifts. Cash handling, opening and closing the store.

EDUCATION

Indiana University, Indiana — Bachelors

Aug 2022- Present

Currently studying for a degree in Informatics

North Central High School, Indiana — Core40 Diploma with Honors

August 2018- May 2022

High school diploma, graduated with 4.3 GPA top 100 in class

SKILLS

Communicator

Social

Adaptability

Creativity

Customer Service

Leadership

Critical Thinking

Problem Solving

Teamwork

AWARDS

Top 15% in graduating high school class

Indiana University Luddy School of Informatics direct admission

Provost-Scholarship (Indiana University)

LANGUAGES

English

Vietnamese